elevationscu.com 2016-05-13

# Privacy Notice

## Elevations Credit Union Privacy Notice 

Facts: Why?

What Does Elevations Credit Union Do With Your Personal Information? Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.

Facts: What?

What Does Elevations Credit Union Do With Your Personal Information? The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include: Name, address, Social Security Number, Account balances and payment history, Credit history. When you are _no longer_ our member, we continue to share your information as described in this notice. 

Facts: How?

What Does Elevations Credit Union Do With Your Personal Information? All financial companies need to share non-public personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their non-public personal information; the reasons Elevations Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.

Reasons we can share your personal information: For our everyday business purposes: Such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus.

Does Elevations CU Share? Yes

Can you limit this sharing? No

Reasons we can share your personal information: For our marketing purposes: To offer our products and services to you.

Does Elevations CU Share? Yes

Can you limit this sharing? Yes

Reasons we can share your personal information: For joint marketing with other financial companies.

Does Elevations CU Share? Yes

Can you limit this sharing? Yes

Reasons we can share your personal information: For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes. Information about your transactions and experiences.

Does Elevations CU Share? Yes

Can you limit this sharing? No

Reasons we can share your personal information: For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes: Information about your creditworthiness.

Does Elevations CU Share? Yes

Can you limit this sharing? No

Reasons we can share your personal information: For our affiliates to market to you.

Does Elevations CU Share? Yes

Can you limit this sharing? Yes

Reasons we can share your personal information: For non-affiliates to market to you.

Does Elevations CU Share? Yes

Can you limit this sharing? Yes

Who is providing this notice? Elevations Credit Union

How does Elevations Credit Union protect my personal information? To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.  
We contractually require all third parties to meet our standards for safekeeping the confidentiality of our members’ financial information.

How does Elevations Credit Union collect my personal information? We collect your personal information, for example, when you: Open an account or Make an electronic transfer, pay your bills or Apply for a loan, use your credit or debit card. We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.

Why can’t I limit all sharing? Federal law gives you the right to limit only: Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes - information about your creditworthiness, affiliates from using your information to market to you, sharing for non-affiliates to market to you. State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.

Affiliates: Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies. We share information with our affiliates for the benefit of our members to provide Trust Services, Lending Services, and Investment Services.

Non-affiliates: Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies. We share information with non-affiliates for the benefit of our members to provide Shared Service Centers and Card Services.

Joint Marketing: A formal agreement between non-affiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you. We enter into joint marketing agreements to provide our members Insurance Services, Auto Broker Services, and Business Services.

### To Limit our sharing of if you have questions:

Call [800.429.7626](tel:8004297626) or [303.443.4672](tel:3034434672)

**Please note:**  
If you are a _new_ member, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this notice. When you are _no longer_ our member, we continue to share your information as described in this notice. However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
